wholesaleforum.com 2015-06-16

# Privacy Policy - Wholesale Forum

### Welcome to Wholesale Forum.com **** ****

#### For Buyers

Wholesale Forum is the fastest growing online business community dedicated to retailers, auction sellers, surplus and overstock buyers needing a quick and safe solution for sourcing trade stock. Join our free and friendly forums today and gain knowledge, offer your advice, and discover new partnership opportunities:

#### For Suppliers

For wholesalers, dropshippers, manufacturers, distributors and trade services providers. Advertise your business today on WholesaleForum.com for free to reach potential trade buyers on a more personal level. Promote your latest offers, interact with buyers in real time, distinguish yourself as an expert in your field, and attract sales instantly.

At WholesaleForum.com we know you care about how your information is treated. We have put in place policies and procedures to ensure your privacy is protected.

Collection and Use of Personal Information

The information you provide helps us improve your sourcing and selling experience. We use this information to manage your account and to communicate with you about our services. We also use this information to prevent abuse of our website.

Does wholesaleforum.com Share the Information It Receives?

Information about our users is an important part of our business, we are not in the business of selling it to others. We may share customer information only as described below, under controls that are either subject to this Privacy Policy or follow practices at least as protective as those described in this Privacy Policy:

  * **Agents:**  
We employ companies to perform some functions on our behalf. Examples include processing credit card payments (banks) and verifying your registered details (registrars). They have access to personal information needed to perform their functions, but may not use it for other purposes. .
  *   
**Protection of WholesaleForum.com and others:**  
We release account and other personal information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, to enforce or apply our [Terms of Use](http://www.wholesaleforum.com/discuss/terms.php) and other agreements, or to protect the rights, property or safety of WholesaleForum.com, our users or others. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organizations for fraud protection. This does not include by any means selling, renting, sharing or otherwise disclosing personally identifiable information from customers for commercial purposes in a way that is contrary to the commitments made in this Privacy Policy.

Information Security

  * We work to protect the security of your information by using 128 Bit Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) transmission, which encrypts information you input using the highest industry security standards.
  * We maintain physical, electronic and procedural safeguards in connection with the collection, storage and disclosure of personally identifiable customer information. Our security procedures mean that we may occasionally request proof of identity before we disclose personal information to you.
  * It is important for you to protect against unauthorized access to your password and to your computer. Be sure to Log Out when you finish using a shared computer.

  * **Remarketing:**

We use AdWords remarketing to market our sites across the web. We place a cookie on a browser, and then a 3rd party (Google) reads these cookies and may serve an ad on a 3rd party site. You may opt out of this ad serving on Google’s opt out page. If you are concerned about 3rd party cookies served by networks, you should also visit the [Network Advertising Initiative opt-out page](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp).

Conditions of Use and Revisions

If you choose to visit WholesaleForum.com, your visit and any dispute over privacy is subject to this Privacy Policy and our [Terms of Use](http://www.wholesaleforum.com/discuss/terms.php), including limitations on damages and application of the laws of the USA. If you have any concern about privacy at WholesaleForum.com, please [send a thorough description](http://www.wholesaleforum.com/discuss/sendmessage.php) and we will try to resolve it.

Our business changes constantly and our Privacy Policy and the [Terms of Use](http://www.wholesaleforum.com/discuss/terms.php) may also change. You should check our website frequently to see recent changes. Unless stated otherwise, our current Privacy Policy applies to all information that we have about you and your account. We stand behind the promises we make, and will never materially change our policies and practices to make them less protective of customer information collected in the past without the consent of affected customers.

All times are GMT -4. The time now is 11:14 PM. \- [Fixed Width](http://www.wholesaleforum.com/discuss/privacy.php?styleid=2)
